Thank you for watching
ME
hmm
mmm
three, two, one...
Three, two, one.
me
3, 2, 1 me
mmm
hn
ELL proprietary Huns
The Demon King lives up to the expectations of the strongest of the AC dossier
Fiber largest total
One person sensor and nament
Thank you for watching!
We are Ice!
We are Ice and we are going to be active from now on!
First of all, let me introduce myself.
My name is Ryosuke Yagami, and my member color is white.
I don't have anything yet, but I will try my best to be a person who deserves your love.
I will do my best to love you all so that I can be a person who deserves your love.
My name is Takizawa, and my member color is purple.
Today is my anniversary with you all.
I will continue to love you all forever!
Yes, I am Ryuto Yamamoto, member color pink.
Please have an unbreakable dream with us!
All of you here
I'll never let anyone go. I'll love you fans as much as I can.
Yes, my name is Toshiaki Atsui, member color orange.
I will bring you energy and smiles with my best performance.
And I will always love your smiles.
Yes, my member color is green, I'm Hiroto Chiyo.
I may not be able to be with you every day, but I will always love you even when we are apart.
Yes, my member color is red, Haruse Evil Sound.
I will turn the gratitude of my fans into passion and love you with all my heart for 100 years and beyond.
Yes, I am Taro Nakamura, member color is yellow.
My member color is yellow, Nakamura Taro.
I always want to be with you in your precious moments.
Let's make precious moments happen together with me and all of you who love me.
I will love you in every moment.
Yes, my member color is blue, Cigaric.
We will be your guide as your smile shines on me.
Please watch us from the ice cream for the rest of your life.
And to all the members, let's love each other a lot from now on.
Please take care of each other.
We are going to make our major label debut with these 8 members!
From this moment on, we will be Ice!
We love you more than anyone else in this world.
And you are indispensable to us, Ice.
As coolers, we want you to love us always by our side.
And now, for the very last time, as a new member of the Ebidan Group
We will perform this song so that you will love us the most.
Heart in Love
Fallin' out During the recording
Fallin' out I'm crazy about you
Brace my heart, brace my heart, are you getting it?
The rain came up, the tears that I dropped, the wind wrapped me up
I'm like a flower blooming by the side of the road
Say my name, I'm you
I'm watching from afar
I can't stop thinking about you Baby, run to you
Just by standing in front of you
I swallow the words I've chosen
It's not as simple as it all comes together
It's not that simple
The only love in the world
I can't say I love you
Even if I catch it, it seems to slip away
I'm in pain
In the endless space
Because you're the one I've come across
I want to get closer
Because I love you so
Easy come, easy go
I'll be by your side
Like this
See, you can't shake me
I want to be with you forever and ever
I just want to smileI just want to smile.
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Can you hear me, baby girl?
In my dreams.
I could always talk to you the way I want to.
Every time I wake up I want to go back
I hate myself for being so timid.
What do you think?
I can't measure my feelings by my attitude.
It's too traumatic.
We're just having fun
We're this time
We're more than friends
I'd like to be sure
But I'm afraid it's all gonna break down
I can't take the first step
The smile you give me
More precious than anything else
I want to protect you
I've learned how to feel
Someday I'll be able to say I love you
So that I can be stronger
I want you to wait for me
Because I love you so
I'm moving away
The only love in the world
I can't say I love you
Even if I catch you, I feel like I'm going to suck you out and it's going to be painful
In the endless coincidences
Because you're the one I've met
I want to get closer to you
Because I love you so
Fall in love all the time
Fall in love so Fall in love
Phrases I repeat in my heart
Are you getting it?
That's all for now, we're ice cream!
Good evening.
Yay!
Good evening!
I'm Yuki from Super Express.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I haven't heard.
I'm not listening...
Today, everyone...
Aisu, congratulations on the final!
Thank you very much.
Oh, no...
On such a memorable day...
I have an important announcement for you all.
I received an important announcement.
What? What? What? What?
I'll read it out loud.
Are you all ready?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God?
Oh, my God!
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa?
Oh!
On Saturday, August 5th, 2023
Ice's first concert will be held!
Whoo-hoo!
Yay!
What?
Well, the name of the concert is...
Ice First Concert.
It's called Ice Love You.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Come on, come on.
And that means
The best of the best is...
900-seat Hulic Hall Tokyo
Well...
I think it's going to be a pretty big game.
Tickets for this event will be available today
from 8:00 p.m. today.
Woohoo!
The first attack will start.
Yes, sir.
Congratulations! Thank you!
Well, as a senior member of the Shrimps...
I'm sorry I startled you.
I'm sorry to surprise you, but... you are now a member of the Shrimp Clan.
I'm sorry to startle you... but you're now officially a member of the Shrimp Clan and we're going to start working as a group.
I'm sure we all have our own personalities and we may or may not meet each other.
I think it's important that we all have the same goals and objectives.
If that is decided, even if there are some fights, as long as everyone is working towards that goal, everyone's individuality will become one, and we will be able to work together in the future.
I'm sure that everyone's individuality will become one, and we'll never stray from the path we've set for ourselves.
I'm sure that we'll be able to go straight ahead
I'm sure we'll be able to go straight ahead
Let's make the place of our dreams the spirit of our words.
I want you to make your dream come true.
I hope that you will continue to make that dream come true.I hope you will continue to make that dream come true.
I hope you can make that dream come true.
So, good luck to all of you from now on.
Thank you very much.
Well then...
As a senior member of the shrimp group...
I said it's fine...
From today onward, that cooler
I'm going to be the "cooler" today!
Yes, it's called a cooler.
Yes...
Yes, that's right.
All of you who are going to be coolers today...
Please support these 8 people.
Thank you very much.
Well, let's take a commemorative photo at the end of the day.
Oh, wow.
Where's the photographer?
Please.
There he is. Here you go.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Well, there you go again.
I'm nervous.
Ko-chan, Ko-chan.
Oh, Ko-chan, I made a mistake.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh~!
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
So, I'm going to leave it here for the last time, but...
Please finish up with me, Shigariku.
Yes, sir.
Where are you?
Wait!
What what what?
What what?
You never told me.
Hmm?
It's my mom's.
Mom's.
Oh, it's my mom's.
Oh, well...
Yes, we are going to change our name to "Eyes" from now on.
Thank you very much.
You and O-chan were very close.
Right?
Yeah.
I've already made the switch.
That's my girl.
You're so cool.
You cried like a baby.
But I finally got it.
I've finally got it... so I'm going to name this group Ice Cream... and all of you coolers...
And to all of you coolers out there...
We love you!
We have our own pose.
This one.
This is Ice.
Ice on the left chest.
Right hand on top.
90 degrees. 90 degrees.
All of you, please remember this.
I'm counting on you.
I know it's a bit sudden.
We've been thinking...
A concert like this.
On a really big stage.
As a sudden surprise.
We're really happy to be able to do it.
and it made us feel like we have to work even harder
I feel like we have to work even harder.
I really want to thank all of you.
We're not coolers... we're not coolers!
We're not coolers, we're fans!
We're ice cream fans!
No, no, no, no, no!
Will you follow us on ice cream?
Will you follow us?
Please don't melt our ice cream.
Oh, my God!
Cool!
That's so cool!
Absolutely raid, absolutely raid.
Well, thank you so much for coming out today.
We're going to do our best as Ice Cream from now on.
So coolers, please follow us!
Okay, that's it for us.
Ice!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Bye bye cooler!
Check us out on SNS!
Follow us on SNS
Follow me on SNSFollow me on social media!
You have to follow me on Instagram.
I'm gonna melt.
Follow me on social media.
Follow us on TikTok too!
SNS
Bye bye!